Contact

azita.afshari@asu.edu

www.linkedin.com/in/azita-afshari-36189064 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Practice

Activism

Farsi

Languages

Persian

Certifications

Healthcare Accreditation Certified Professional

Lean Six Sigma Yellow Belt (ICYB)

Registered Nurse

Certified Medical-Surgical Registered Nurse (CMSRN)

Honors-Awards

Graduated Magna Cum Laude

Outstanding Representative in Community Involvement

Azita Afshari

MSN, RN, CMSRN, HACP

Greater Los Angeles Area

Summary

A confident and proficient board certified Registered Nurse at Cedars-Sinai Medical Center. Passionate in enhancing the nursing profession through quality projects and performance improvement. Masters-prepared specializing in leadership and Yellow belt certified in Lean Six Sigma.

Experience

Cedars-Sinai

3 years 1 month

RN Surveillance Specialist

October 2019 - Present (9 months)

Los Angeles, California

Registered Nurse

June 2017 - October 2019 (2 years 5 months)

Greater Los Angeles Area

Loma Linda University Medical Center Registered Nurse March 2016 - June 2017 (1 year 4 months)

Loma Linda, CA

Aya Healthcare

Travel Nurse

March 2015 - March 2016 (1 year 1 month)

Seattle, WA

March 2015 - June 2015

Seattle, WA

July 2015 - October 2015

Loma Linda, CA

St. Joseph's Hospital and Medical Center

Page 1 of 2

3 years 2 months

RN, BSN

September 2012 - March 2015 (2 years 7 months)

Phoenix, Arizona

Nurse Extern

February 2012 - September 2012 (8 months)

Mayo Clinic Clinical Immersion July 2012 - August 2012 (2 months) Phoenix, Arizona

Education

Western Governors University

Masters of Science in Nursing, Leadership / Management · (2018 - 2020)

Arizona State University

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2012)